《大白鲨3》
来吧，慢点！ 快点！
Come on, slow poke! Come on!
不要向前倾！ 不要向前倾！
Don't lean forward! Don't lean forward!
来吧，长官 让我们休息一下，好吗？
Come on, Overman. Give us a break, will you?
看小丑 穿着运动短裤！
Look at the clown in the jockey shorts!
凯莉，来吧 注意
Kelly, come on. Pay attention.
嘿，姑娘们！
Hey, girls!
这样做！
Do it like this!
该死，凯莉！ 做这项工作！
Damn it, Kelly! Do the job!
下次我们一起去 去泻湖的路
Next time we're goin' all the way into the lagoon.
泻湖是我的最爱！
The lagoon is my favorite!
该死的船 我淹没了
Damn boat. I flooded the…
该死的船！
Damn boat!
来吧，里奇 我今晚有个约会！
Come on, Richie. I got a date tonight!
来吧，宝贝
Come on, baby.
好了，伙计们，开始吧
Okay, guys, here we go.
哦！这是正确的很好
Oh! That's right. Good.
你被选为 队友们为了你的整洁，
You've been chosen as teammates for your neatness,
以礼相待 所有人，你的南方恩典
courtesy toward others and above all, your Southern grace.
我们在这里执行着装规定，
We enforce our dress code here,
所以留着你的头发 修剪指甲
so keep your hair and nails trimmed.
拜托了， 不要改变你的服装
And, please, don't alter your costumes.
一旦你安装了 你的海洋世界导游服，
Once you've been fitted with your Sea World guide apparel,
短裤够短了
the shorts are short enough.
只要你有脸，你就会 反铲炸薯条-
Show any cheek and you'll be back shovelin' French fries-
现在，让我们继续欢迎 再说一遍现在都在一起
Now, let's continue with our welcome speech again. All together now.
欢迎来到海洋世界，
Welcome to Sea World,
世界上最大的 海洋生物公园
the world's largest marine life park.
上下表面 我们独特的海底王国
Above and below the surface of our unique Undersea Kingdom…
公园正式启用 星期六开门
The park officially opens on Saturday.
整个星期都是，而且 继续，预告周，
All this week has been, and continues to be, preview week,
在这期间家人和朋友 作为我们的客人参加海洋世界
during which family and friends attend Sea World as our guests.
这是海底王国，
This is the Undersea Kingdom,
在建四年 花费超过3400万美元
four years under construction, at a cost of more than $34 million.
四个加压观察通道 辐射到泻湖
Four pressurized viewing tunnels radiate out into the lagoon.
那是沉没的西班牙人 加伦，约拿的海上游乐场，
There's the Sunken Spanish Galleon, Jonah's Marine Fun House,
深海珊瑚林 连接到集线器，中央控制
the Deepwater Coral Forest, all connected to the hub, Central Control.
还有一家豪华餐厅 还有鸡尾酒厅，
And a deluxe restaurant and cocktail lounge,
都在水面下40英尺
all 40 feet below the surface.
整个建筑群都建成了 在我们的人工湖里，
The whole complex is built in our manmade lagoon,
连接到开放的 通过深水航道的海洋
which is connected to the open ocean by a deepwater channel.
海洋世界的新增加 是个聪明的孩子
The new additions to Sea World are the brainchild.
企业家卡尔文？布沙尔
of entrepreneur Calvin Bouchard.
嗨，伙计们！
Hi, guys!
现在你可以关上门了
Now you can close the gate.
天哪！
Jesus!
奥夫曼，我以为你说过 那些铁轨很安全
Overman, I thought you said those tracks were secure.
嘿，伙计们，我焊接了 那该死的东西我自己
Hey guys, I welded the damn thing myself.
门上挂着什么东西
Something's hung the gate up.
最好把迈克？布罗迪弄出去 孩子，他会生气吗
Better get Mike Brody out here. Boy, is he gonna be pissed.
谁！
Whom!
这是泻湖 准备转弯
Here's the lagoon. Set up for the turn.
我提醒你注意 对于海洋世界的滑雪者来说，
I call your attention to the Sea World skiers,
即将 进入泻湖
who are about to enter the lagoon.
在 开幕式
in a preview of the opening day ceremonies.
我的骄傲和快乐来了
Here come my pride and joy.
我们能不能 有机会和布查德先生谈谈吗？
Are we gonna get a chance to talk to Mr. Bouchard?
- 很漂亮真漂亮！ - 嗨！
- Beautiful. Just beautiful! - Hi!
不过，我们希望 避免提及他丰富多彩的过去
We would, however, like to avoid references to his colorful past.
海底王国 真的花了3000万美元？
Did the Undersea Kingdom really cost $30 million?
那些孩子不是很好吗？
Aren't those kids great?
布查德先生，有什么事吗 特别是在开放日吗？
Mr. Bouchard, is there anything speciai goin' on openin' day?
今天下午， 在大门口，
Well, this afternoon, at the main gate,
我们很高兴宣布
we'll be pleased to announce.
欢迎 菲茨罗伊斯先生
the welcomin' of Mr. Philip FitzRoyce.
哦，真的吗？是真的吗？
Oh, really? Is that true?
别撒谎，孩子们他会来的 现在，我们在酒吧有饮料
No lie, boys and girls. He gonna be here. Now, we got drinks at the bar.
他们自由了来吧， 跟着我
They free. Come on, follow me.
奥夫曼，看起来怎么样？
Overman, what's it look like?
它偏离了轨道
It's off the track.
怎么会这样？
How'd that happen?
我不知道，但她被卡住了
I can't tell, but she is jammed.
只是关不上，迈克
Just wouldn't close, Mike.
现在我们该怎么办？
Now what are we gonna do?
哦，孩子
Oh, boy.
有人敲了 狗娘养的马上离开跑道
Somethin' knocked the son-of-a-bitch right off the track.
好吧，看只是安全 该死的大门，好吗？
Well, look. Just secure the damn gate, all right?
你能应付吗？
Think you can handle that?
可能是加班费
On overtime, maybe.
也许是正点时间？ 你加班够了
Straight time maybe? You got enough overtime.
你的派对 你买啤酒吧，布罗迪
Your party. You buy the beer, Brody.
好吧，听着，你负责
Well, look, you're in charge.
待会儿见我得到了 更重要的事情要做-
See you guys later. I got more important things to do-
不加班
No overtime.
可以再见，迈克
Okay. See you, Mike.
不准加班！
No overtime!
嗨，迈克
Hi, Mike.
哦啊嘿，丹 嘿
Oh. Ah. Hey, Dan. Hey.
有门问题吗？
Havin' gate problems?
海豚试过 再打开一次
The dolphins tried to open them again.
老板呢？
Where's the boss?
她和沙姆在一起
She's up with Shamu.
谢谢
Thanks.
来吧，辛迪
Come on, Cindy.
来吧，桑迪来吧
Come on, Sandy. Come on.
嘿，利兹
Hey, Liz.
嘿来吧
Hey. Come on.
是老板的安全帽 你的靴子呢？
It's the boss hard hat. Where's your boots?
我只穿它们睡觉 在洗澡的时候
I only wear 'em to bed and in the shower.
凯在哪？ 她在那边
Where's Kay? She's down that way.
是啊哈！
Yea-haw.!
骑着他们，牛仔
Ride 'em, cowgirl.
嗨，迈克！ 嘿！
Hi, Mike! Hey!
我会和你在一起 马上，亲爱的
I'll be with you in a minute, darlin'.
好吧
All right.
用你的马刺
Use your spurs.
嘿，利兹！
Hey, Liz!
好孩子太好了！
Good boy. That was nice!
嘿 嘿！
Hey. Hey!
利兹，他做得很好 我不想再这样了
Liz, he did that great. I don't wanna do it again.
帮我一个忙
Do me a favor.
把辛迪和桑迪放在泻湖里 快跑，好吗？他们越来越胖了
Put Cindy and Sandy in the lagoon for a run, okay? They're getting fat.
可以
Okay.
你怎么做？ 太好了
How you dam"? Great.
嘿，你过来
Hey, you. Come here.
过来，孩子 那是喂食的地方
Come here, kiddo. That's the feeding place.
这是鲸鱼吗 房子坏了吗？
Is this whale house-broken yet?
不
Nope.
那他就不能来吃饭了
Then he can't come to dinner.
你带我去吃饭？
You takin' me to dinner?
是的，很快我们 去接我弟弟
Yeah, soon as we pick up my brother.
肖恩什么时候来？
When's Sean coming?
他在公园的穿梭机上我们是 在大门口等他
He's on a park shuttle. We're gonna meet him at the main gate.
嘿，凯西
Hey, Kathy.
辛迪和桑迪不想去
Cindy and Sandy don't wanna go.
什么，我会失去你 几条神经质的鱼？
What, am I gonna lose you to a couple of neurotic fish?
哺乳动物 哺乳动物哺乳动物
Mammals. Mammals. Mammals.
好像有什么东西 去窃听他们
Something seems to be bugging 'em.
好吧，听着 现在是他们的游戏时间
Well, listen. It's their play time.
如果他们不想要，他们会 明天求我们把它们放上去
If they don't want it, they'll be beggin' us tomorrow. Put 'em up.
你明白了
You got it.
今晚我求你了
I'm begging you tonight.
你不必乞求
You don't have to beg.
带我去吃晚饭吧！
So take me to dinner!
好吧我们尝尝寿司吧
All right. Let's try sushi.
迈克！ 我要换衣服
Mike! I'll change.
过来 谁是好孩子？
Come here. Who's a good boy?
你是个好孩子吗？ 是的，你是个好孩子
Are you a good boy? Yes, you're a good boy.
你得到一条鱼
And you get a fish.
女士们 先生们，他来了
Ladies and gentlemen, here he is now.
女士们先生们，菲利普先生 菲茨罗伊斯，有首都
Ladies and gentlemen, Mr. Philip FitzRoyce, with a capital.
是来拍我们的，认识我们 住院日科研人员
is here to film us, meet our resident day scientific staff.
嘿，这是什么？ 哦，不
Hey, what's this? Oh, no.
菲利普大帝
Philip the Great.
当然，我可以组合 愉快地做生意，
I am, of course, able to combine business with pleasure,
他们告诉我 幸福长寿的秘诀
which, they tell me, is the secret to a long and happy life.
什么，菲茨罗伊斯？
What, FitzRoyce?
嗯
Mmm.
当然是
Sure is.
现在，女士们先生们，请继续 如果你愿意的话，可以在酒吧里提问
And now, ladies and gentlemen, any further questions, in the bar, if you please.
第一次 谁买的，对吧？
For the first one who buys one, right?
看看卡尔文最好的朋友 啊，最好的朋友
Look at Calvin. Best of buddies. Ah, best of friends.
一个普通的巴纳姆和贝利
A regular Barnum and Bailey.
我相信他们会的 在一起很开心
I'm sure they'll be very happy together.
很完美 嗯-嗯
Perfect. Mmm-hmm.
进入海底 他们去的王国
Into the Undersea Kingdom they go.
嘿，米奇！
Hey, Mikey!
嘿新的嘿 哦！
Hey. new Hey' om!
你好吗？ 好吧！
How you doin'? All right!
我哥哥，那个牛仔
My brother, the cowboy.
嘿！拥抱我，嗯？
Hey! Hug me, huh?
哦，好吧 嘿
Oh, Okay. Hey.
你体重增加了，你需要一个 刮胡子你就太高了
You put on weight, you need a shave and you're too tall.
三分之二 我能修好
Well, two out of three I can fix.
拿上那个装备，我们走 来吧
Get that gear and let's go. Come on.
那么，漂亮的靴子
So, nice boots.
谢谢！哦，天啊
Thanks! Aw, gee.
我简直不敢相信我竟然那样做了
I can't even believe I did that.
你期末考试考得怎么样？
How'd you do on your finals?
伟大的绅士 不完整，但我比Phys好预计起飞时间
Great. A gentleman's an incomplete, but I aced Phys. Ed.
一个真正的爱因斯坦
A real Einstein.
很高兴你来了，伙计
Glad you're here, buddy.
好了，查理
There you go, Charlene.
谢尔比出现了吗？
Shelby showed up yet?
没见过他
Haven't seen him.
他们在做什么？
What are they doing?
凯莉真的 把这个放下
Kelly's really gettin' this one down.
看到那边那个大个子了吗？他 每天晚上都会被打屁股
See that big guy over there? He gets knocked on his ass every night.
好吧，查理 好吧！
All right, Charlene. All right!
我来帮你 和我一起工作，和我一起工作
Here, let me help you out. Work with me, work with me.
走吧
Let's go.
好了 等待再一个
There we go. Wait. One more.
嘿，迈克 好吧是啊？
Hey, Mike. All right. Yeah?
谢尔比在加班吗？
Is Shelby workin' overtime?
不是我说的他应该 别跟其他人说了
Not on my say-so. He was supposed to knock off with the rest of the guys.
你见过我弟弟吗？
Have you met my kid brother?
如果他搞砸了 在纪念品摊上撒尿，
If he's messin' around with that little bitch down at the souvenir stand,
会是他的屁股
it's gonna be his ass.
你告诉他
You tell him.
沙琳，我不是他妈妈
Charlene, I'm not his mother.
你是他的老板
You're his boss.
是的，问问伍德伯里，好吗？
Yeah, ask Woodbury, okay?
快点，凯莉 你能做到的！
Come on, Kelly. You can do it!
嘿，他们 对峙
Hey, they're playing stand-off.
哦哦
Uh-Oh.
我哥哥认为自己是 新英格兰的杰出冠军
My brother considers himself to be the stand-off champion of New England.
以及西部各州
And the western states.
去拿吧
Go get 'em.
嘿，我还没准备好！
Hey, I wasn't ready!
我告诉你， 这是一场平衡的游戏
I tell you, it's a game of balance.
我告诉过你他会摔倒的
I told you he'd fall on his ass.
嘿，这家伙是谁？
Hey, who's this guy?
这是给啤酒的 你买了吗？
This is for beers. You buyin'?
准备好了吗？ 嗯哼
Ready? Mm-hmm.
我的苍蝇开着
My fly's open.
不公平！
No fair!
谁！
Whom!
嗯，呃，
Well, it's, uh,
不仅仅是一场平衡游戏， 这是一场骗局
not only a game of balance, it's a game of deception.
来吧，我给你们买两个 为了你欠我的那个
Come on, I'll buy you two for the one you owe me.
可以 好吧
Okay. All right.
好吧
All right.
再见，凯莉
See you later, Kelly.
嘿，我要你来吧， 马上！走吧
Hey, I want you. Come on, right now! Let's go.
凯瑟琳，迈克
Kathryn, Mike.
你好 你好
Hi. Hi.
你们认识吗？
You know each other?
我看到我哥哥把你钉死了，是吗？
I see my brother nailed you, eh?
你弟弟？是啊， 信不信由你
Your brother? Yeah, believe it or not.
如果他不拉那么老的话 裤裆魔术，他永远不会赢-
If he wouldn't have pulled that old crotch trick, he never would have won-
这是他最好的举动
That's his best move.
在家里跑步
Runs in the family.
好吧，成功了
Well, it worked.
我们喝什么？
What are we drinkin'?
香槟 工人阶级
Champagne of the working classes.
啤酒你呢 欠我一对
Beer. And you owe me a couple.
这就是战斗 启动
That's fight. Comm' up.
两杯啤酒所以，你工作 在公园，嗯？
Two beers. So, you work at the park, huh'?
嗯-嗯 我是滑水运动员
Mmm-hmm. I'm a water skier.
哦
Oh.
你弟弟很可爱
Your brother's cute.
是啊他和凯瑟琳 一起呆了一年半
Yeah. Him and Kathryn have, uh, been together for a year and a half.
你呢？
How about you?
孤立无援
Desperately unattached.
孤独，困惑
Lonely, confused.
慷慨而爱有缺点 都在我眼里
Generous and loving to a fault. It's all in my eyes.
- 来吧 - 男23好的
- Come On. - MAN 23 Okay.
我们会警察很多 今晚真不错
We'll cop a lot of good stuff tonight.
我有坦克
I've got the tanks.
嘘！
Shh!
车在这儿还好吗？
Is the van okay here?
是的，没关系
Yes, it's okay.
我们是海洋世界的财产 没人用这条路
We're off Sea World property. Nobody uses this road.
嘘！
Shh!
是啊
Yeah.
好吧
All right.
是啊
Yeah.
翻过篱笆，然后 放轻松点
Climb over the fence, and take it easy with the raft.
该死的！
Damn it!
你这个混蛋
You asshole.
现在我们要把它全部拖走 去水里的路！
Now we gotta drag it all the way down to the water!
准备好了吗？
Ready to go?
可以谁付钱？
Okay. Who's payin'?
啊
Ah.
小心蛇
Watch out. Snakes.
哦，来吧 别胡说我
Oh, come on. Don't bullshit me.
鸡肉，嗯？
Chicken, huh?
好的，稳住
All right, steady.
稳定 知道了
Steady. Got it.
可以给你
Okay. Here we go.
来吧，划桨！
Come on, paddle!
我是
I am.
我们到中心去吧
Let's go out to the center.
我真希望这是值得的
I sure hope this is worth it.
嘿，凯莉，这是你的车吗？
Hey, Kelly, is this your car?
当然是
Sure is.
嘿滚开！
Hey. Get off of there!
你想散散步吗？是啊
You wanna take a walk? Yeah.
嘿，小弟弟呢？
Hey, what about baby brother?
啊！ 啊！
Aww! Aww!
小弟弟
Little baby brother.
凯利，你能载他一程吗 回家，还是给他妈妈打电话？
Kelly, can you give him a ride home, or shall I call his mommy?
不，如果他能安静地来
Nah, if he'll come quietly.
不可能我又叫又叫
No way. I scream and shout.
哦，天哪，外面真臭 我们走吧！
Oh, God, it stinks out here. Let's get away!
再见
See ya.
嘿，我们去游泳吧
Hey, let's go swimming.
不，我讨厌大海
No, I hate the ocean.
啊！嘿，我有 更好的主意
Aww! Hey, I've got a better idea.
像泻湖？
Like lagoons?
泻湖？
Lagoons?
泻湖
Lagoons.
哦为什么肖恩 不多看吗？
Oh. How come Sean doesn't visit more?
他讨厌水 什么？
He hates the water. What?
是啊记得我说过的鲨鱼袭击 你是说我们小时候和睦相处吗？
Yeah. Remember that shark attack I told you about when we were kids in Amity?
所以他才去 去科罗拉多上学
Well, that's why he goes to school in Colorado.
如果我们的父母不住在岛上， 我想他不会淋湿的
If our parents didn't live on an island, I don't think he'd ever get wet.
我爸爸，他也是
My dad, he's the same way.
天哪，我爱这地方
God, I love this place.
我讨厌当 我们第一次来这里
I hated it when we first came here.
怎么了
What's the matter?
你接到电话了吗？
Did you get a telephone call?
委内瑞拉？
Venezuela?
我想我必须 开始学西班牙语
Guess I'm gonna have to start learning Spanish.
哦，宝贝 是啊是啊
Ooh, baby. Yeah. Yeah.
太好了 太好了
That's wonderful. That's wonderful.
哦，妈的
Oh, shit.
现实
Reality.
多长时间？
How long?
短短一年半
Just a short year and a half.
我希望你能来，你知道的
I'd love you to come, you know.
是啊
Yeah.
但是那六个呢 我还剩下几个月
But what about the six months I've got left here.
工作开始了 在斯克里普斯学院？
and the job opening up at the Scripps Institute?
那怎么办？嗯？
What about that? Huh?
很简单放弃吧 你的生活跟我来
Simple. Just give up your life and follow me.
哦，我很高兴 为你林
Oh, I'm happy for you. lam.
我知道你是
I know you are.
我们该怎么办？
What are we gonna do?
哈哈 嗯哼
A-ha. Mm-hmm.
来吧
Come on.
哦，我不下水
Oh, I don't go in the water.
你不游泳？
You don't swim?
连朋友都没有？
Not even with friends?
哦，呃，lswim 我只是，呃，我一、 …
Oh, uh, lswim. I just, uh, I… I…
是这样的 发生在我小时候
It's something that happened when I was a kid.
我只是，我不下水
I just, I don't go in the water.
我打赌我能克服 你童年的恐惧
I bet I can overcome your childhood fears.
我打赌你可以
I bet you can.
来吧
Come on.
我的靴子！
My boots!
把他们赶走，牛仔
Kick 'em off, cowboy.
凯利！
Kelly!
进来吧，肖恩 很有趣
Come on in, Sean. It's fun.
来吧
Come on.
在这里？
Here?
是的，好的
Yeah, okay.
在下面的某个地方 是最好的珊瑚
Somewhere down there is the best coral.
迈阿密的人会给我们 好东西200美元
A guy in Miami will give us $200 for the good stuff.
把它放进篮子里 我把它拉上来
Put it in the basket. I'll pull it up.
快点，兰迪
Come on, hurry, Randy.
我喜欢晚上的公园 太冷清了
I love this park at night. It's so deserted.
是啊太安静了
Yeah. So quiet.
等等 那不是凯利的车吗？
Wait a second. Isn't that Kelly's car?
停，停，停 嘘！等等
Stop, stop, stop. Shh! Wait a second.
停下来
Stop.
嘘
Shh.
我不相信
I don't believe it.
她把他弄下水了
She got him in the water.
永远不要低估 权力，嗯？
Never underestimate the power, huh?
注意你，在水里你是 侵犯海洋世界的财产
Attention. You, in the water. You are trespassing on Sea World property.
带着你的 双手举过头顶
Come out of the water with your hands raised high above your head.
我没事 我哥哥在这里工作
I'm okay. My brother works here.
呃，我是凯莉？安？布可夫斯基， 来自滑雪队
Uh, I'm Kelly Ann Bukowski, from the ski team.
你们火鸡有身份证吗？
You turkeys have any ID?
等一下
Wait a minute.
迈克？凯？ 兄弟？
Mike? Kay? Brother?
牛角先生看到了一切， 全都知道！
Mr. Bullhorn sees all, knows all!
你死定了！
Dead is what you are!
你把手放好 对你自己来说，年轻人
You keep your hands to yourself, young m…
给，拿着这个
Here, take this.
喊妈妈！
Yell for mother!
快下来，该死！
Finish up down there, damn it!
来吧，兰迪 我们得离开这里！
Come on, Randy. We gotta get out of here!
现在怎么办？
Now what?
噢！
Ow!
迈克！
Mike!
你这个骗子！
You cheater!
那就是 你是！死了！
That's what you are! Dead!
有些人可以睡 在早上
Some guys can sleep in in the morning.
我们有些人得早点上班 早上好
Some of us have to be at work early. Good morning.
我们中的一些人不需要照看孩子 公园里到处都是蛞蝓和鱼
Some of us don't have to baby-sit a park full of slugs and fishes either.
是的，我们就像蛞蝓和鱼一样生活 早上好，麦琪
Yes, we just live like slugs and fishes. Good morning, Maggie.
这条狗不在柜台上吃东西
The dog does not eat on the counter.
我把你的湿衣服 在烘干机里，亲爱的
I put your wet clothes in the dryer, sweetie.
谢谢 嗯我们吃什么？
Thanks. Mmm. What are we eating?
嗯谢谢您
Mmm. Thank you.
嘿，这是我的呼机吗 还是你的呼机？
Hey, is this my beeper or your beeper?
我不知道 我用这个传呼机
I don't know. I'll use this beeper.
用那个传呼机
Use that beeper.
以后再跟你说
Talk to you later.
我要我的呼机 叫你的呼机
I'll have my beeper beep your beeper.
我要我的呼机 传呼你的传呼机回来
I'll have my beeper beep your beeper back.
再见 再见
Bye. See you later.
是的
Aye.
咖啡？
Coffee?
把它扔到我的眼睛里， 它会工作得更快
Just throw it in my eyes, it'll work faster.
是啊，就是这样 当你熬夜的时候
Yeah, well that's what happens when you stay up all night.
解决你的问题 儿童恐惧症
workin' out your childhood phobias.
这是正确的开玩笑 你的小弟弟
That's right. Make fun of your baby brother.
但我就要这么做了 昨晚在水里，
But I was this close to doing it in the water last night,
这是第一次
and that's a first.
就这么近，嗯？ 闭嘴！
This close, huh? Shut up!
哦，对不起我没有 知道是治疗-
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't know it was therapy-
承认吧 你把我搞砸了
Just admit it. You messed me up.
我承认 我把你搞砸了
I admit it. I messed you up.
一切都好吗 你和凯瑟琳之间？
Is everything all right between you and Kathryn?
你好？
Hello?
是的，先生
Yes, sir.
卡尔文，我有我的船员 就在昨天
Calvin, I had my crew on that yesterday.
嗯，我知道我不想 这也会发生
Well, I know. I don't want that to happen either.
明天
Tomorrow.
好吧，好吧加尔文， 我马上就到
Okay, Okay. Calvin, I'll be right there.
老板，对吧？
The boss, right?
我得去上班了
I gotta go to work.
是啊，再好不过了！ 真正地
Yeah, can't do better than that! Really.
是啊是啊！
Yeah. Yeah!
谁是好女孩？ 那是我的孩子
Who's a good girl? That's my baby.
凯？
Kay?
辛迪和桑迪怎么样？
How are Cindy and Sandy?
好吧，辛迪没事， 但桑迪还是很紧张
Well, Cindy's okay, but Sandy's still nervous.
不要放弃，丹尼 他可以走得更高
Don't quit, Danny. He can go higher.
就这样！
That's it!
好吧，姑娘们 有我的女儿
Okay, girls. There are my girls.
谢谢您来吧 准备出发！
Thank you. Come on. Ready and go!
就这样
That's it.
这是什么？准备好了吗？ 我说走！
What is this? You ready? I said go!
如果这些是最好的行为， 我不想看到最坏的情况
If those are the best behaviors, I'd hate to see the worst.
需要帮忙吗？
May I help you?
你在找人吗？
Are you looking for somebody?
不，我不认为你能我是 寻找有权威的人
No, I don't think you can. I'm looking for someone in authority.
好吧，我是摩根医生， 高级生物学家
Well, I'm Dr. Morgan, the senior biologist.
哦
Oh.
真的？
Really?
很迷人菲茨罗伊斯
Charming. Philip FitzRoyce.
我认识你 我知道你的工作
I know you. I know your work.
我们是在遵守海洋法 去年夏天一起开会
We were at that Law of the Sea Conference together last summer.
哦，是的，没错赫尔辛基 拯救鲸鱼
Oh yes, that's right. Helsinki. Save the Whales.
他们把我塑造成英雄
They made a hero out of me.
是的，你知道吗 我不明白？
Yeah, you know what I never understood?
你为什么要撞车 那个日本捕鲸船？
Why did you ram that Japanese whaler?
因为他进来了 我的方式，毁了我最好的机会
Because he got in my way, ruined my best shot.
是啊我印象深刻
Yeah. I was impressed.
很好也许我们可以 今晚喝点什么晚餐？
Good. Then perhaps we can have a drink and some dinner tonight?
哦，对不起，菲茨罗伊斯先生，但是， 我就是不这么做-
Oh, I'm sorry, Mr. FitzRoyce, but, that's a behavior I just don't do-
旋转得很好，丹尼我会见面的 你在储藏室
Nice spins, Danny. I'll meet you at the holding tank.
嘿水女孩！
HEY. aqua girl!
嗨，迈克！
Hi, Mike!
五个
Five.
他不睡觉， 他不住在里面
He don't sleep in, he don't live in.
替我告诉谢尔比？奥夫曼 他能飞起来
Tell Shelby Overman for me he can take a flyin' leap.
在一个面包圈上 碎石车道，听到了吗？
at a rollin' doughnut on a gravel driveway, you hear?
等一下没有 他昨晚回家了？
Hold it just a second. Didn't he come home last night?
他也没出现在这里 不
He didn't show up here either. No.
我想他回家的时候已经醉醺醺的了
I figure he's home hung over.
我告诉你，那个男人的垃圾，我 别让他在我家附近！
I tell you, the man's trash, and I don't want him around my place!
他走了 你拿走他的东西
He's gone. You take his stuff.
查琳，怎么了？
Charlene, what's goin' on, huh?
谢尔比？奥夫曼又来了
Shelby Overman's AWOL again.
哦，不，对不起
Oh, no. I'm sorry.
什么，这都是他的东西吗？
What, is this all his stuff?
是啊不知道
Yeah. Doesn't figure.
他把护照和 还有他的信用卡
He left his passport and his… And his credit cards.
驾照，当票
Driver's license, pawn tickets.
我觉得他不可能 计划太过分了
I don't think he could have been planning to go too far.
你不认为 他出事了？
You don't think something happened to him?
我是说，难道 警方已经
I mean, wouldn't the police have called…
不不，看他蜷缩着 起来，在某个地方喝醉了
No. No, look. He is curled up, drunk someplace.
当我找到他时， 他有大麻烦了
And when I find him, he's in deep trouble.
别担心我们会让你 我们一听到什么就知道
Don't you worry. We'll let you know as soon as we hear anything.
想帮我吗？
Wanna help me out?
是啊小心点，查理
Yeah. Take care, Charlene.
帮我看看泻湖？
Help me look in the lagoon?
当然
You bet.
嘿，我生那个老男孩的气了， 但我不是故意伤害他
Hey, I'm mad at that old boy, but I don't mean him any harm.
听到了吗？ 我不是故意伤害他！
You hear me? I don't mean him any harm!
再往下一点
Down a little more.
转动它
Turn it.
电池是 充满电了，迈克
Batteries are fully charged, Mike.
谢谢你，丹尼
Thank you, Danny.
谢谢，丹尼
Thanks, Danny.
潜水控制室 正在进入泻湖
Control room, submersible is now entering the lagoon.
罗杰我可以监视 从这里开始
Roger. I can monitor it from here.
谢谢
Thank you.
测试，一个， 二，三你能读懂我吗，凯？
Testing, one, two, three-Can you read me, Kay?
我看到你了 沟通很好
I read you. Communication's fine.
为了沙琳， 我真希望他没事
For Charlene's sake, I sure hope he's all right.
辛迪还是桑迪？
There's Cindy or Sandy?
我不知道怎么做 把它们分开
I don't know how to tell them apart.
凯”辛迪要大得多
KAY". Cindy's a lot larger.
控制，这是第一次冒险
Control, this is Venture One.
我们在25英尺的地方 西班牙大帆船
We're at 25 feet, headed for the Spanish Galleon.
我现在可以见到你了 嗨，迈克
I can see you now. Hi, Mike.
奥夫曼违反了潜水员的规则 昨晚，在外面
Overman broke divers' rules last night, out there.
被戴上镣铐 只有海门
Went down to shackle the sea gate alone.
如果他出了什么事，大海 水流会把他冲到这里来，
If anything happened to him, the ocean current would have washed him up here,
朝向泻湖的中心
toward the center of the lagoon.
过滤管呢？
What about the filtration pipes?
不，太强了a 电流向相反方向移动
No, it's too strong a current moving the other way.
看，所有的流程 进入泻湖
See, the flow's all into the lagoon.
有一百万加仑 每小时提供新鲜盐水
There's a million gallons of fresh salt water every hour.
你觉得他应该 被困在西班牙大帆船里？
You think he could have gotten trapped in the Spanish Galleon?
他本来可以 困在上层建筑中
He could have gotten caught in the superstructure.
会留下他 从浮式平台上部
Would have kept him from floating topside.
迈克！哦，天哪 我想……
Mike! Oh, God. For a second I thought…
是的，是的我知道 我们叫他奥斯卡
Yeah, yeah. I know it. We call him Oscar.
你留在这里，凯我将进入 加隆，仔细看看
You stay here, Kay. I'll go into the galleon and take a closer look.
呃，呃，迈克 我和你一起去
Uh-uh, Mike. I'm goin' with you.
该死的海豚！什么 他们到底在干什么？
Goddamn dolphins! What the hell are they doing?
我不知道他们已经 最近两天表现得很奇怪
I don't know. They've been acting strange for the last two days.
看看他们
Look at 'em.
控制，我们离开潜艇
Control, we're leaving the sub.
我们将失去无线电联系
We'll be out of radio contact.
听你说， 摩根博士
Read you, Dr. Morgan.
抓住你的腹肌瓶， 凯我们走吧
Grab your ABS bottles, Kay. Let's go.
凯”好的，亲爱的
KAY". Okay, sweetie.
- 快走！ - 快走！
- Go! - Go!
迈克！快点！迈克！
Mike! Quick! Mike!
大门！去开门！ 鲨鱼！
The gate! Get the gate! Shark!
上帝啊！V发生什么事了？
God! Vvhat' s happening?
快，该死！接近！
Close, damn it! Close!
倒霉！
Shit!
哦，天哪！你没事吧？ 那是什么鬼东西？
Oh, God! Are you okay? What the hell was that?
是啊！那是什么？ 你还好吧？
Yeah! What is that? You okay?
我的爱人 哈登菲尔德的第16位伯爵
My guv'nor's the 16th Earl of Haddenfield.
与第一个握手 海洋世界的加尔文
Shake hands with the first Calvin of Sea World.
附魔附魔他 你也懂法语吧？
Enchante. Enchante. He Know French too, huh'?
对不起，先生们 布查德先生
Excuse me, gentlemen. Mr. Bouchard…
等一下 我们在这里吃晚饭
Wait a minute. We're havin' dinner here.
这最好是重要的 是的，先生
This better be important. It is, sir.
迈克和摩根医生 被叛变的鲨鱼追赶
Mike and Dr. Morgan were pursued by a renegade shark.
它进入了我们的泻湖
that got into our lagoon.
很重要，先生们 最好跟我来
It is important, gentlemen. Better come with me.
相信我，卡尔文， 这是一个伟大的白色
Believe me, Calvin, it was a great white.
它大约有十英尺长 表现出典型的进食模式
It was about ten feet long, it was exhibiting a typical feeding pattern.
在我们身上，卡尔文！
On us, Calvin!
那该死的东西想喂我们 例如
The damn thing tried to feed on us. Exacfly.
现在看 它在哪里？
Now look. Where is it?
就在这里
Right here.
嗯？
Huh?
你知道吗，卡尔，这个 可能是运气
You know, Cal, this could be a stroke of luck.
如果我们杀了这个野兽 在摄像机上，
If we kill this beastie on camera,
我可以向你保证 媒体报道
I can guarantee you media coverage.
把他引到集结地，
Lure him into a staging area,
就在此时此刻， 把他的肚子剖开
and at the precise moment, slit his belly wide open.
你能做到吗？
Can you do that?
你试着阻止他，伙计
You try and stop him, mate.
我们就是这样挣钱的
That's how we earn our bread.
好吧，杰克过于简单化了 像往常一样重要
Well, Jack is oversimplifying matters, as is usual.
但是，是的，我能做到
But, yeah, I can do that.
- 不！ - 没有？
- No! - No?
你什么意思，不？
What do you mean, no?
我不知道是不是 你们中的任何一个，
Well, I don't know if it's occurred to any of you all,
但是没有一个很好的白色 被囚禁在任何地方
but there isn't a great white alive in captivity anywhere.
现在，我们是独一无二的， 卡尔文，你知道的
Now, we're unique here, Calvin, you know that.
如果任何设施可以 保持白色，是我们
If any facility can maintain a white, it's us.
如果我们能射他，让他安静下来， 我们可以把他放进一个贮槽
If we could dart him, tranquilize him, we could get him in a holding tank…
别动！这太疯狂了， 这太疯狂了
Hold it! This is crazy, this is nuts.
白鲨是杀手 我认识他们
White sharks are killers. I know 'em.
我父亲，我兄弟，我自己
My father, my brother, myself.
他们是杀人犯不，凯
They're murderers. No, Kay.
卡尔文，他们死得很漂亮
Calvin, they die magnificently.
那真是一个壮观的事件 毫无疑问，嗯？
That would really be a spectacular event. No doubt about that, huh?
我们在做什么，卡尔文， 策划网络特辑？
What are we doing, Calvin, planning a network special?
你不知道我们可以 成为地球上的第一个人
Don't you realize that we could be the first people on the planet.
有一个伟大的白人活着
to have a great white alive.
如果我的丈夫 小姐，先去拿吧
Not if my guv'nor gets it first, miss.
可以说他杀了它 好吧，就这样
Okay. Say he kills it. Well, that's it.
一枪打完就没了
It's one shot, over, gone.
但是一个活生生的白人现在， 你想想看，卡尔文！
But a live great white. Now, you think about that, Calvin!
晚间新闻 鲨鱼杀手的进展
Nightly bulletins on the progress of the killer shark.
我们护理它的照片 恢复健康
Pictures of us nursing it back to health.
降低它 进入一个储存罐
and lowering it into a holding tank.
现在，这是世界新闻！
Now, that's world news!
想想门口的队伍
Think of the lines at the gate.
那你就错过了 杀人的运动
Then you miss the sport of the kill.
现在，等等，杰克 等等
Now, wait up, Jack. Wait up.
杀戮是媒体的保证
Killing is guaranteed press.
但另一个很重要， 更有趣
But this other is much, much more interesting.
可以， 我是MS-222
Okay, this is MS-222.
这是奎纳定，但我有 估计剂量
This is quinaldine, but I had to guesstimate the dosage.
凯西？
Kathy?
正确的谢谢，丹尼
Right. Thanks, Danny.
好了，我们准备好了 掌控一切你们都准备好了吗？
All right, we're ready in Control. You all set?
我们已经准备好了
We're ready down here.
好吧，有了这些 电视监视器滚动，
Well, with those TV monitors rolling,
你会有更多的报道 比这附近的太空发射更重要
you're gonna have more coverage than a space launch around here.
很好就像我喜欢的那样 正确的
Good. Just the way I like it. Right.
你湿衣服的颜色 一个地狱般的选择
The color of your wet suit's one hell of a choice.
鲨鱼会爱你的
The shark's gonna love you.
确切地
Exactly.
它帮助我 拍特写镜头
It helps me get the close-ups.
你是表演家
You're the showman.
亲爱的，你觉得这个 西装能保护你吗？
Honey, you think this suit's gonna protect you?
你在开玩笑吗？ 你有没有感觉到
Are you kidding? Have you felt the…
它咬不穿， 但它会屈服于压力
It won't bite through, but it will yield to pressure.
所以她可能会 稍微挤一下
So she might just get a little squeeze.
哦，真是个好消息听着， 你为什么要这么做？
Oh, that's great news. Look, why do you have to do this?
为什么不让女王陛下 一号儿子搞定，嗯？
Why don't you let Her Majesty's number one son take care of it, huh?
因为这是我的工作，记得吗？
Because it's my job, remember?
是的，但我只是不 希望是你
Yeah, but I just don't want it to be you.
听着，所有的东西都是你造的，我游泳 在里面就是这样对吗？
Look, you build all the stuff, I swim around in it. That was the deal. Right?
隐马尔可夫模型？
Hmm?
我也爱你
I love you, too.
如果我们遇到任何麻烦 我们要做的就是拔出别针
If we get into any trouble, all we have to do is pull the pin.
- 这些是什么？ - 米尔斯炸弹
- What are those? - Mills bombs.
什么？ 米尔斯炸弹，桑尼
What? Mills bombs, sonny.
手榴弹女王陛下的一个小伙子 军械弥补了rne的不足
Grenades. A chap in Her Majesty's ordnance makes them up for rne.
小克莱莫尔斯- 良好的水平分散性
Baby claymores- Good horizontal dispersion.
有些脑震荡有点粗糙 鼓膜，但它们起作用
Some concussion. A bit rough on the eardrums, but they do the trick.
好吧，不是在我的水里 把它们取下来
Well, not in my water. Take 'em off.
你喜欢编织，我的 亲爱的，我会照顾我的
You tend to your knitting, my dear, and I shall tend to mine.
别动 稍等一下
Hold it. Hold on a second there.
不会有 任何水下爆炸物
There's not gonna be any explosives underwater.
下面是丙烯酸树脂， 这是一个非常脆弱的环境
There's acrylic down there, it's a very fragile environment.
没有炸弹
There's no bombs.
听着，布罗迪，我知道 这是保险……
Look, Brody, I do inderstand. This is insurance…
不，我不认为你 理解我，菲茨罗伊斯！
No, I don't think you understood me here, FitzRoyce!
我花了两年时间做这个 停车，我不去看
I spent two years building this park, and I'm not gonna see.
有个消防队员 自制炸弹把它炸了
some visiting fireman with a homemade bomb blow it up.
只是因为他想 杀了一条鱼！
just because he wants to kill a fish!
卡尔文，你是 听着这些？
Calvin, are you listening to all this?
没有手榴弹
No grenades.
看在上帝的份上，古诺 还记得澳大利亚吗？
For Christ's sake, guv'nor. Remember Australia?
哦，别担心，杰克
Oh, don't worry, Jack.
毕竟，只是 一条小鱼
After all, it's only a little fish.
儿子
Son of a…
必须拔出销子
The pin has to be pulled.
正确的摆脱 这些东西的
Right. Get rid of this stuff.
船上所有人？ 我们走吧
Everybody aboard here? Let's get going.
走开
Shove off.
我需要一个干净的腹部注射
I need one clean belly shot.
如果我错过了第一关， 我得重新加载
If I miss on the first pass, I'm gonna have to reload.
希望我能抓住他 用第二个飞镖
and just hope I get him with the second dart.
这是一个很好的开始
This is a good place to start.
打电灯
Hit the lights.
我们跳舞好吗？
Shall we dance?
是啊，为什么不呢？我开始觉得 就像理查德国王参加十字军东征一样
Yeah, why not? I'm beginning to feel like King Richard going to the Crusades.
准备好了吗，杰克？ 去拿装备
Ready, Jack? Get the gear.
棕色面包，古夫纳
Brown bread, guvnor.
你还好吧？
You all right?
祝你好运
Good luck.
你知道你只有一次机会
You know you only get one shot.
是的，我知道 我知道
Yeah, I know. I know.
凯瑟琳呢？
What about Kathryn?
它会粘在鲨鱼身上击中 她，然后就过去了
It'll stick in the shark. Hit her, and it'll go right through.
让他振作起来， 让他慢下来，对吧？
Just buoy him up, slow him down, right?
背鳍，背部中部
Dorsal fin, middle of the back.
看到什么了吗？
Seen anything yet?
是的，我们会抓住他的 在监视器上
Yeah, we'll get him on the monitors.
快点！迈克， 他跑了！
Quick! Mike, he's making a run!
快，开枪打他！
Quick, shoot him!
他要走了！
He's getting away!
该死的！
Damn it!
让开，凯！
Get out of the way, Kay!
现在！
Now!
来吧
Come on.
正确的给你
Right. There you go.
你做到了，宝贝 你做到了
You did it, baby. You did it.
这是梯子 等等
Here's the ladder. Hold on.
来吧 把你的鳍给我
Come on. Give me your fins.
把你的鳍给我 我们走吧！
Give me your fins. Let's go!
你上去吧
Up you go.
你还好吧？
You all right?
在后面关上一个
Close one back there.
让我们把这些东西从她身上拿下来
Let's get this stuff off her.
凯，太好了！
Kay, that was great!
我是什么，该死的搬运工？
What am I, a bloody porter?
帮个忙怎么样 用这个硬件？
How about a hand with this hardware?
不，第一件事，杰克
No, first things first, Jacko.
不能忽视女士们
Mustn't ignore the ladies.
不要忽视 救命恩人
And don't ignore the bleedin' help.
下面看起来毛茸茸的
Looked pretty hairy down there.
你还好吧，凯？为了 一秒钟，我很担心
You all right, Kay? For a second, I was so worried.
你当然知道 把我吓跑
You sure know how to scare the hell out of me.
一定要把他包好，好吗？让他淋湿 让我们把他放进坦克里
Be sure he's wrapped, okay? Keep him wet. Let's get him in a tank.
拍电影好吗？ 电视画面看起来阴云密布
Film all right? TV picture looked cloudy.
加尔文凯瑟琳很好， 菲利普没事，杰克没事
Calvin. Kathryn's fine, Philip is fine, Jack is fine.
丹和利兹很好 我也很好
Dan and Liz are fine. I am okay too.
但是，这部电影还好吗？
But, is the film okay?
绝对是 一流的，卡尔
It's absolutely first-rate, Cal.
我想你会很高兴的
I think you'll be very happy.
大家都好吗？
Is everyone okay?
看起来很漂亮 下面很危险
It did look pretty dangerous down there.
是啊，看起来很危险 从下面也来，卡尔文
Yeah, well, it looked pretty dangerous from down here too, Calvin.
我们可能得对付他 整晚，让他动起来
We may have to work him all night, keep him moving.
下来，丹尼下来，下来 就这样
Down, Danny. Down, down. That's it.
我们必须确认氧气 一直在他的腮缝里跑
We have to be sure the oxygen keeps running through his gills.
我们不想失去他
We don't wanna lose him.
关上门！不管你是谁 是的，这是禁区
Close the door! Whoever you are, this is off limits.
利兹，呃，把水管打开我 想给他充气吗？
Liz, uh, get the hose running. I wanna try aerating him, okay?
即使对我来说， 无畏的鱼叉手？
Even to me, the fearless harpoonist?
不，你没事
Nah, you're okay.
进来吧，水手 你是新来的吗？
Come on in, sailor. Are you new in town?
是啊过来接我 一个女人和一个纹身
Yeah. Came by to get me a woman and a tattoo.
想看看纹身吗？
Wanna see the tattoo?
好吧，我宁愿去见那个女人， 看看比赛
Well, I'd rather see the woman, get a look at the competition.
对不起，没有别的女人， 也没有纹身
Sorry, there isn't any other woman, there isn't any tattoo either.
我很孤独
I'm lonely.
对不起，该死的
I'm sorry, damn'.
该死的哺乳动物
Damn mammal.
这条是鱼
This one's a fish.
一条简单美丽的鱼
A simple, beautiful fish.
可以
Okay.
迈克！迈克！你在做什么？ 你疯了吗？
Mike! Mike! What are you doing? Are you crazy?
利兹，去远足 可以
Liz, take a hike. Okay.
如果这是唯一的办法 我们可以在一起，
If this is the only way we can be together,
这是唯一的办法 我们可以在一起
this is the only way we can be together.
欢迎上船，水手明白了 用水龙带抓住它，好吗？
Welcome aboard, sailor. Get that hose and hold onto it, okay?
是啊可以 张开嘴
Yeah. Okay. Open the mouth.
向你的新朋友问好
Say hi to your new friend.
你知道，这是第一次 你曾经和我一起工作过
You know, this is the first time you've ever done my work with me.
是的，嗯，真是太刺激了
Yeah, well, it's a real thrill.
也许明天你 可以和我一起工作
Maybe tomorrow you can come work with me.
有一些真正的兴奋 帮我打地基
and have some real excitement help me pour foundations.
逃掉！让开！ 让开！
Get away! Get clear! Get clear!
哇哦！
Whoa!
他没有给你任何信号吗？
Didn't he give you any signs?
不！一分钟 他死定了，
No! One minute he was dead out,
下一分钟 他完全清醒！
the next minute he was wide awake!
没有食物 没有药物治疗
No food. No medication.
它是唯一被囚禁的活生生的，伙计们 让我们让他一直这样
It's the only live one in captivity, guys. Let's keep him that way.
呵呵？不做任何事 那会给他带来创伤的
Huh? Don't do anything that's gonna traumatize him.
嗨，伙计们欢迎来到 海底王国的开放
Ahoy, mateys. Welcome to the opening of the Undersea Kingdom.
约拿的神奇奥秘 鲸鱼，珊瑚林
The magical mysteries of Jonah and the Whale, the Coral Forest.
以及沉没的西班牙大帆船
and the Sunken Spanish Galleon.
明白了，老兄！
Gotcha, guv'nor!
它是一头鲸鱼 大脑比大多数人都大，
It's a whale with a brain larger than most folks,
能赚大钱 一次装订
able to earn beaucoup bucks in a single bound.
凯和我在潜艇里，
Kay and I went down in the sub,
我们搜索了 整个地区
and we searched over all this area.
在鲨鱼袭击我们之前
before the sharks hit us.
是的，但是迈克，如果奥弗曼去了 在海门的另一边？
Yeah, but Mike, what if Overman went down on the other side of the sea gate?
潮水可能 把他拉出来，
The tide might have pulled him out,
但我们应该去看一场人体秀 在海岸的某个地方
but we should have had a body show up somewhere along the coast.
布罗迪，你查过了吗 过滤管？
Brody, did you check the filtration pipe?
不，卡尔文当前的 另一条路
No, Calvin. The current's too strong goin' the other way.
我们有一百万加仑的海水 每小时流入泻湖
We got a million gallons of sea water flowing into the lagoon every hour.
这个人不负责任 当他出现时，解雇他
The man's irresponsible. When he turns up, fire him.
等等，卡尔文 别动
Hold it, Calvin. Hold it.
他是个好人他只是搞砸了 偶尔起来
He's a good man. He just messes up every once in a while.
我会坚持 你负责隐马尔可夫模型？
I'm gonna hold you responsible. Hmm?
现在，她可以去滑雪了 因为帕蒂是最好的
And now, she gets to ski by herself because Patty's the best.
怎么样，伦纳德？我只是 得到今天的第一份打印件
How's it going, Leonard? I just got today's first print-outs.
今天，我们的预售额是三 比我们的其他公园早了一倍
Today, our advance sales are three times ahead of our other parks.
不意外，伦纳德 大白鲨现在在哪里？
Not unexpected, Leonard. Where's the great white now?
在储藏室里我想把 他在第六泳池展出
In the tank room. I want to put him on display at pool six.
我想告诉大家 把所有的信息
I wanna instruct everyone to put all that information.
在所有的欢迎声中， 休息和总结
on all the welcomes, rest stops and wrap-ups.
但我以为我们要等 关于摩根博士的话
But I thought we were to wait on Dr. Morgan's word for that.
看我经营公园，我卖 票是我决定的
Look. I run the park, I sell the tickets and I make the decisions.
把鱼挪开！
Move the fish!
我想站出来 三点前排队看
I wanna be able to stand in line to see it before three.
三下， 向上，然后转身
Three and down, and up, and turn.
现在， 海洋世界滑水队
And now, the Sea World water ski team.
令人眼花缭乱 协调与卓越
in a dazzling display of coordination and brilliance.
银色子弹！
The Silver Bullets!
好吧！ 很好！
All right! Lookin' good!
他们来了！
There they go!
是啊！直升机！
Yeah! The helicopters!
嗨，肖恩 你真的很性感
Hi, Sean. You were real hot.
你真的很性感
You were real hot.
我想让我们单独呆一会儿你 演出间隙有几分钟吗？
I want some time for us alone-You got a few minutes between shows?
当然 太好了，凯莉
You bet. Great, Kelly.
听 准备好好玩了吗？
Listen. Ready for some fun?
好极了！ 让我们乘碰碰船吧
Fantastic! Let's ride the bumper boats.
碰碰船？
Bumper boats?
来吧，这很有趣
Come on, it's fun.
这是入口 对于海底王国，
This is the entrance to the Undersea Kingdom,
不可思议的情结 水下隧道
an incredible complex of underwater tunnels.
给你看第一手资料 深渊的奇迹
that show you first-hand the miracles of the deep.
没有额外费用 为了这个独特的吸引力
There's no extra charge for this unique attraction.
我们的水下隧道 不仅有趣，而且信息丰富
Our underwater tunnels are not only fun, but informative.
哦，看看那个
Oh, look at that.
在历史上被活生生地消耗掉， 约拿知道是什么样的
Consumed alive in history, Jonah found out what it was like.
生活在 海洋是最伟大的动物
to live in the belly of the ocean's greatest animal.
我们特别的约拿和鲸鱼 展览时间为11：00、1：00和4：00
Our special Jonah and the Whale showcase is at 11:00, 1:00 and 4:00.
在圆形剧场 在海底王国中
in the amphitheater inside the Undersea Kingdom.
这是船长的水槽
This is Captain Sink.
欢迎来到我的洞穴 充满乐趣和惊喜
Welcome to my cave of fun and surprises.
哦，恶心！
Oh, yuck!
我肯定会想念这些家伙的
I sure am gonna miss these guys.
怎么样，卡斯帕？
How 'bout it, Casper?
你想拿着钱跑 和老米奇去委内瑞拉？
You wanna take the money and run to Venezuela with old Mikey?
比斯卡多安静吗？ 你会说西班牙语，嗯？
Quieres un pescado? You speak Spanish, huh?
我想他们会 我也很想你
I think they're gonna miss you, too.
现在你和我必须 一次严肃的谈话
Now you and I are gonna have to have a serious conversation sometime…
关于到底发生了什么
About what's really goin' on.
你和我
You and me.
我知道我知道
I know. I know.
迈克？布罗迪迈克？布罗迪 请给办公室打电话
Mike Brody. Mike Brody. Call your office, please.
再见
See ya later.
海洋世界， 为了纪念开幕日
Sea World, in honor of opening day…
哦，卡斯帕
Oh, Casper.
女孩该怎么办？
What's a girl to do, huh?
谢谢您
Thank you.
大白鲨 在6号游泳池中
A great white shark in holding pool number six.
你可以看到那个 只有被囚禁的伟大白人
You will be able to view the one and only great white in captivity.
大白鲨 在海洋深处漫游
The great white shark has roamed the ocean's depths.
千百万年来
for millions of years.
骄傲的动物……
A proud animal…
请原谅我哦，天哪！
Excuse me. Oh, God!
独处时，是一个掠食者…
While alone, is a predator…
请原谅我！ 他在这里干什么？
Excuse me! What is he doing here?
卡尔文命令他搬走
Calvin ordered him moved.
他为什么不问我？为什么？ 他是一个人去的吗？
Why didn't he ask me? Why did he go ahead on his own?
这条鲨鱼，a 首次举办……
This shark, a first of its kind to be held…
不，丹尼！丹尼！
No, Danny! Danny!
利兹，准备好水管， 我现在就给他充气！
Liz, get a hose ready, I wanna aerate him now!
来吧，丹尼去后面
Come on, Danny. Get the back.
女人”请稍等 请保持冷静
WOMAN". Just a minute. Please remain calm.
摩根博士和助理 我们的员工
That's Dr. Morgan and assistant members of our staff.
呃，请不要干涉 以任何方式
Uh, please don't interfere in any way.
请原谅我
Excuse me.
利兹！利兹！
Liz! Liz!
来吧，孩子
Come on, boy.
就这样来吧 转过来，丹尼
That's it. Come on. Turn it, Danny.
倒霉！ 来吧快点！
Shit! Come on. Come on!
不，孩子，快点！
No. Boy, come on!
请原谅我
Excuse me.
女人”让我把你的 注意其他一些事件…
WOMAN". Let me bring your attention to some other events…
凯瑟琳
Kathryn.
海豹水獭秀 当然还有……
The seal and otter show and of course…
凯瑟琳
Kathryn.
运气不好
Bad luck.
前进 拍下来
Go ahead. Photograph it.
留神！ 凯利凯利
Look out! Kelly. Kelly.
我不知道 我不知道不不
I don't know. I don't. No. No.
来吧，你会喜欢的 很有趣相信我快点！
Come on, you'll love it. It's fun. Trust me. Come on!
这是什么东西？ 你确定吗？
What is this thing? Are you sure?
你确定吗？ 我们应该这么做吗？
Are you sure we should be doing this?
哦！哦，天哪这个能吗 抱两个人？
Oh! Oh, God. Can this hold two people?
哦推动推动
Oh. Push. Push.
哦，天哪你是吗 还是我在操纵这个？
Oh, my God. Are you steering this, or am I?
快走！快走！逃掉！醒悟
Go! Go! Get away! Get awayi.
我们邀请你进入魔法世界 深海珊瑚林世界
We invite you to enter the magical world of the deepwater Coral Forest.
在那里你可以观察到 深而不湿
where you may observe the wonders of the deep without ever getting wet.
西班牙大帆船扮演主人 给无数色彩斑斓的鱼
The Spanish Galleon plays host to a myriad of colorful fish.
那个海洋世界 世界上不同的海洋
that Sea World has assembled from the different oceans of the world.
看看他们所有人！ 哦，是的！
Look at all of them! Oh, yeah!
看起来像只蝴蝶 你说得对
That looks like a butterfly. You're right.
哦，天哪！ 看那个！
Oh, my God! Look at that!
听着，凯，我不认为 你想看看这个
Look, Kay, I don't think you want to see this.
迈克，大家都在假设 这是鲨鱼袭击
Mike, everybody is assuming that this was a shark attack.
不，我想确定一下 可以好吧
No, I wanna make sure. Okay. All right.
你们把他拉出来了吗？
Did you guys pull him out?
那是谢尔比？奥夫曼
That's Shelby Overman.
凯，我告诉过 错过
Kay, I told… Miss…
迈克雷
Mike. Ray.
如果这是鲨鱼袭击， 我以前见过
If this was a shark attack, I've seen it before.
可以？
Okay?
哦，迈克
Oh, Mike.
哦，天哪！
Oh, my God!
让我们去找卡尔文 快点！快点！
Let's go find Calvin. Come on! Come on!
我变得很矛盾 过滤泵的读数
I'm getting a lot of contradictory readings from the filtration pumps.
比如说？
Such as?
高泵速，低流量
High pump rate, low outflow.
压力增大 在内侧通道阀上
and a pressure build-up on the inboard tunnel valve.
那是第二个 可能是障碍物
That's number two. Could be an obstruction.
嗯，那不是我的部门
Well, that's not my department.
看看你能不能找到布罗迪 或者卡尔文，好吗？
See if you can locate Brody or Calvin, will you?
很时髦
Very posh.
是的，这是一个很好的展示
Yes, it's quite a display.
告诉我如何控制 在泻湖的这个地方有鲨鱼吗？
Tell me. How do you contain the sharks in this part of the lagoon?
那是老鲨鱼的屏幕， 那个泡沫屏风
It's that old shark screen, that bubble screen.
你知道的， 鲨鱼不喜欢那样
You know, sharks don't like that.
他们称之为海军陆战队 隔离
It's what they call, uh, marine segregation.
布查德医生电话
Dr. Bouchard. Telephone.
对不起，先生们 现在舒服点
Ah, excuse me, gentlemen. Get comfortable now.
给你，先生
Here you go, sir.
布查德在这里
Bouchard here.
水泵呢？
What about the pumps?
啊，不，不，不 不要等布罗迪
Ah, nah, nah, nah. Don't wait for Brody.
只是，呃，关掉二号泵 切换到第一位-
Just, uh, shut down number two pump and switch over to number one-
就这么简单
Simple as that.
因为它太贵了 它们都烧坏了，这就是为什么！
Because it costs too much to replace and they burn out, that's why!
告诉布罗迪下来 海王星双人房，听到了吗？
And tell Brody to get down here to the Neptune Room on the double, y'hear?
谢谢您 不客气
Thank you. You're welcome.
好吧，先生们
Well, gentlemen.
下巴
Chin-chin.
哦，干杯 干杯
Oh, cheers. Cheers.
他们来了
There they are.
卡尔文，我有个坏消息保留 你的声音，坐下
Calvin, I've got bad news. Keep your voices down, sit down.
坐下来！
Sit down!
是鲨鱼吗？
Was it the shark?
是鲨鱼
It was a shark.
咬入半径 大约一码宽
with a bite radius about a yard across.
别傻了这表明 大约35英尺长的鲨鱼
Don't be silly. That would indicate a shark of some 35 feet in length.
你说得没错
You said it exactly.
我们的鲨鱼还有它所有的牙齿 是啊
Our shark still has all its teeth. Yeah.
也就是说那是个婴儿
That means it was a baby.
我们的鲨鱼 杀死了奥夫曼
Our shark couldn't have killed Overman.
它的母亲做到了
Its mother did.
你在谈论 一些该死的鲨鱼妈妈？
You talkin' about some damn shark's mother?
卡尔文，你没听到 她在这里说什么？
Calvin, don't you hear what she's sayin' here?
我在听！
I'm listening!
如果真有这样的动物，
Now, if there is such an animal,
她在海上分娩，
she gave birth way out to sea,
孩子在游泳 穿过海门
and the baby swam through the sea gate.
你开着门，布罗迪！
that you left open, Brody!
不！奥夫曼被杀了 在公园里
No! Overman was killed inside the park.
孩子被抓住了 在公园里
The baby was caught inside the park.
它的妈妈在公园里
Its mother is inside the park.
她就在那儿！
She's right there!
那东西是怎么进去的？
How did that thing get in there?
动物们在泻湖里！ 滑雪表演！
The animals are in the lagoon! Ski show!
控制中心，我是布查德
Control, this is Bouchard.
现在你仔细听我说！
Now you listen to me carefully!
我要你清理隧道，
I want you to clear the tunnel,
我想要你 让人们出去，
I want you to let the people out,
我要你关门 把门关上，封锁公园！
I want you to close the gate and seal the park!
封锁公园！ 我马上就下来
Seal the park! I'll be down in a minute.
嘿！嘿！小心点！
Hey! Hey! Watch it!
- 那家伙是谁；？ - 小心！
- Who is that guy'? - Watch out!
嘿，把它拿过来！嘿！
Hey, bring it over here! Hey!
好吧我已经玩够了 我们现在进去吧
All right. I've had enough fun. Let's go in now.
来吧你很享受这一切
Come on. You're enjoying this.
不，听着，你不必 是在工作还是什么？
No. Look, don't you have to be at work or something?
塔米在金字塔上我没有 回到下半场
Tammy's on the pyramid. I don't have to be back till the second half.
哦 来吧
Oh. Come on.
明白了，亲爱的
Gotcha, lovers.
倒霉！ 上帝啊
Shit! God.
走出！走出！ 嘿，怎么了？
Get out! Get out! Hey, what the?
嘿，你在干什么；？
Hey, what are ya doin'?
布罗迪！
Brody!
离开水里 走出！
Get out of the water. Get out!
请离开水 请，从水里进来
Get out of the water, please. Please, come in from the water.
从水里出来！快点！ 离开水！
Out of the water! Come on! Get out of the water!
从水里出来！
Out of the water!
走出！
Get out!
让开！
Get outta the way!
倒霉！
Shit!
这是海洋世界控制中心
This is Sea World Control.
啊哈
Uh-huh.
对他就在我这儿
Yes. I got him right here.
好吧，孩子们 进来鞠躬吧
All right, boys. Come on in and take a bow.
很抱歉让你 不！快上来！
I apologize to have you… No! Get up here!
从水里出来！ 从水里出来！
Get outta the water! Get outta the water!
孩子们孩子们！
Boys. Boys!
把船拉进来！ 从水里出来！
Bring the boat in! Get outta the water!
您将同时获得 我们在这里开火了！
You're gonna get both of us fired out here!
走出！大家都出去！
Get out! Everybody out!
把麦克风给我！
Gimme the mike!
嘿，布罗迪！回来！
Hey, Brody! Come back here!
从水里出来！ 把它拿进来
Get outta the water! Bring it in.
把它拿进来！ 把船拉进来！
Bring it in! Bring the boat in!
马上离开水！
Get out of the water right now!
准备好了，起来！一个两个
Ready, up! One. Two.
把船弄进来！ 马上离开水！
Bring that boat in! Get outta the water right now!
嘿，把我弄下来！ 把我弄下来！
Hey, get me down! Just get me down!
把我弄下来！ 你在说什么？
Get me down! What are you saying?
后面有东西！ 鲨鱼！
There's something back there! A shark!
把你的船带进来！
Bring your boat in!
那里有一条鲨鱼！
There's a shark!
一，二，三， 四，五，六，七
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
从水里出来！
Get outta the water!
哦，天哪！
Oh, my God!
从水里出来！
Get outta the water!
走出！
Get out!
我们回来了！ 我们回来了！
We're coming! We're coming!
它会吃掉我们的！
It's gonna eat us!
他们会死的！
They'll die!
把你的手给我快点！ 把我拉出来！
Gimme your hand. Come on! Pull me out!
坚持！
Hang on!
需要窒息 或者别的什么拉它
Needs a choke or something. Pull it.
握住我的手
Hold my hand.
凯利！ 鲨鱼！
Kelly! Shark!
凯利！
Kelly!
那是什么鬼东西？ 倒霉！坚持！
What the hell is that? Shit! Hang on!
怎么了？她快淹死了！ 她快淹死了！
What happened? She's drowning! She's drowning!
游泳！游泳，孩子，游泳！
Swim! Swim, kid, swim!
叫救护车
Call an ambulance.
迅速地来吧 让开！
Quickly. Come on. Get out of the way!
请给我们一些房间
Give us some room there, please.
找个医护人员！
Get a paramedic!
小心点，妈妈！
Look out, Mommy!
凯利！
Kelly!
你叫救护车了吗？ 是的，医护人员
Did you call an ambulance? Yeah, the paramedics.
扭动止血带 紧紧地抓住它
Twist that tourniquet tight and hold it there.
该死的鲨鱼！
Goddamn shark!
我来了 你会没事的
I'm here. You're gonna be okay.
还有一些 在水中受伤
There's still some injured in the water.
他们把伤员带回来
They're bringin' in the wounded.
救护车在路上
The ambulance is on the way.
我可以让大门开着吗？ 辛迪和桑迪在外面
Shall I leave the gate open? Cindy and Sandy are out there.
倒霉
Shit.
不，他们必须 照顾好自己，利兹
No. They're gonna have to take care of themselves, Liz.
我们不能冒险 在那个大婊子身上
We can't take our chance on that big bitch gettin' in.
嘿，你还好吧？ 是啊是啊我很好
Hey, you all right? Yeah. Yeah. I'm fine.
呃，我要和凯莉一起去
Uh, I'm gonna go with Kelly.
我认为你应该
I think you should.
你打算怎么办？ 我不知道
What are you gonna do? I don't know.
你好啊 我是卡尔文？布沙尔
Hello out there. This is Calvin Bouchard.
我可以吗 请注意
May I please have your kind attention.
由于技术上的困难，
Due to technical difficulties,
这对我们来说是必要的 暂时关闭
it has become necessary for us to temporarily close.
海底王国现在
the Undersea Kingdom now.
为了你们所有人 这个公园的水下部分，
For those of you all still in the underwater portion of this park,
请遵循您的指导，
please follow your guides,
他们会指出 方便且无障碍的出口
and they will point out the most convenient and accessible exits.
最近的地方在哪 无障碍出口？我们在水下！
Where the hell is the nearest accessible exit? We're underwater!
关了吗？ 啊哈
Is this off? Uh-huh.
给我下面的灯！ 就在这里
Gimme some lights down there! Got them right here.
看不到下面的屎！
Can't see shit down there!
给我拿点药 注意这里，快！
Get me some medical attention here, quick!
好的，女士们先生们，
Okay, ladies and gentlemen,
你们都听到通知了， 所以请跟我来
you all heard the announcement, so please follow me.
以有序的方式， 记住走路，不要跑
in an orderly fashion, and remember walk, do not run.
爸爸，爸爸！ 看那条鱼！
Daddy, Daddy! Look at the fish!
看！ 天啊！
Look! Holy shit!
隧道故障，6号
Tunnel failure, number six.
是约拿和鲸鱼 就这样
It's Jonah and the Whale. That's it.
管道完整性 妥协的
Tube integrity has been compromised.
我们有漏洞 以及压力损失
We've got leakage and pressure loss.
我们得封锁这个区域
We have to seal the section.
否则我们会失去整个情结
or we'll lose the whole complex.
水密门击中它 自动启动
Watertight doors. Hit it. On automatic.
他们都是随叫随到的人 激活现在！
They're all on go status. Activated. Now!
我需要我的钱包！
I need my wallet!
安静的！安静的！拜托！
Quiet! Quiet! Please!
我需要你的注意， 拜托安静的！
I need your attention, please. Quiet!
现在水不流了 再高一点，冷静点，好吗？
Now the water is not going any higher, so calm down, okay?
它停止了信息技术 停下来，冷静点
It's stopped. It's stopped, so calm down.
我们的氧气 我们只有这里，
The oxygen that we have in here is all we have,
所以，让我们不要惊慌，而要尝试 浅呼吸，好吗？
so let's not panic, but let's try to take shallow breaths, okay?
- 嘿，迈克 - 是啊！
- Hey, Mike. - Yeah!
这是我们最后一次切我想我们 隧道补丁已经准备好了
This is our last cut. I think our tunnel patch is ready to go.
很好安装绞盘 在上面的工作船上
Good. Rig the winch on that work boat up there.
你明白了
You got it.
还要多久，亲爱的？ 我不知道
How much longer, sweetie? I don't know.
不？
No?
我们将不得不推动这些 隧道段在一起
We're gonna have to nudge these tunnel sections together.
然后我们要打补丁 我们要把整个焊接起来
Then we're gonna slap on a patch and we're gonna weld the whole thing.
然后我们撤离？
Then we evacuate?
不，那我们得施加压力 回到隧道里，
No, then we gotta put pressure back into the tunnels,
那么水密门就会 打开门，然后人们回家
then the watertight doors will open up, then people go home.
嘿，看你怎么把那东西切下来！ 很关键！
Hey, watch how you're cutting that thing! It's critical!
放松点放松点你在做什么 尽你所能
Relax. Relax. You're doing everything you can.
来吧过来
Come on. Come over here.
听 我一直在想
Listen. I've been thinking.
也许委内瑞拉可以利用 一些训练有素的鲸鱼，嗯？
Maybe Venezuela can use some trained whales, huh?
什么？你是认真的吗？ 是啊
What? Are you serious? Yeah.
我想这件事由我负责
I think this one's on me.
但明年 我会跟你到任何地方
But next year… I'll follow you anywhere.
是啊！ 我爱你！
Yeah! I love you!
啊，格拉斯先生
Ah, Mr. Glass.
是布查德先生吗 会在这里吗？
Is Mr. Bouchard going to be here?
拜托，拜托 我有话要说
Please, please. I have a statement to make.
有爆炸吗？ 那火呢？
Was there an explosion? What about the fire?
有多少人失踪？
How many people are missing?
今天下午晚些时候 小干扰的结果，
Late this afternoon, as a result of a minor disturbance,
有一个压力故障 水下隧道之一
there was a pressure failure in one of the underwater tunnels.
那是一个主要的吸引力 在公园里
that are a major attraction here at the park.
我们估计有30到40个人
We estimate that 30 to 40 people.
正在进行中 被疏散
were in the process of being evacuated.
当水密安全门 暂时推迟了他们的离开
when the watertight safety doors temporarily delayed their exit.
我们现在正在工作 释放他们
We're working right now to release them.
在最安全的情况下 可能的情况
under the safest possible circumstances.
此外，还有7位访客 在我们的海滩上受伤了
In addition, seven visitors were injured in our beach area.
现在就这些了 孩子们，让我休息一下
That's all for now. Give me a break, boys.
我们听说了什么 关于一条大鲨鱼？
What is this we've heard about a large shark?
我会让你知道我知道的更多 一条很大的鲨鱼
I'll let you know as I know more. A very large shark…
仅此而已再也没有了
That's all. There is no more.
他们什么时候能修好这个？
When will they get this fixed?
我相信他们正在努力
I'm sure they're working on it.
呆在一起保暖 我知道你很冷
Stay together to keep warm. I know you're cold.
呆在一起，深呼吸 集中精力呼吸，好吗？
Stay together, take shallow breaths and concentrate on your breathing, okay?
嗯，有妈妈的迹象吗？
Well, any sign of mother?
好吧，那么
Okay, then.
动物在哪 第一次躲起来？
Where did the animal hide the first time?
休斯敦大学
Uh…
过滤管
Filtration pipe.
泻湖的对面
Opposite side of the lagoon.
布罗迪，有通道吗 舱口，反洗门？
Brody, is there an access hatch, a backwash gate?
很重的烤架
Heavy grillwork.
当 我们反冲洗那个系统
Keeps the pumps clear when we back-flush that system.
为什么？你想做什么？ 把那东西拿回来？
Why? What do you want to do? Get that thing back in?
他是个聪明的小伙子
He's a bright lad.
对杰克和我要 把他引回烟斗里，
Yes. Jack and I are going to lure him back into the pipe,
关上门然后 我们有空就把他处理掉
close the gates and then dispose of him at our leisure.
同时，你可以焊接 你的隧道补丁
Meanwhile, you can weld your tunnel patch.
然后卡尔文可以 疏散平民
and then Calvin can evacuate the civilians.
如果她不做呢&apos；t 想回去吗？
What if she doesn't want to go back in?
哦，我想我们可以 保证她会想回去的
Oh, I think we can pretty much guarantee she'll want to go back in.
别这样，杰克？ 当然
Don't you, Jack? Sure.
你还好吗 会保证吗？
Just how are you going to guarantee that?
活饵
Live bait.
我们准备好行动了 现在在隧道那边
We're ready to move out over the tunnel now.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我会在控制室
I'll be in the Control Room.
我和你一起去
I'll go with you.
把那个给我 让我把它放在这里
Give me that. Let me stow it over here.
不，我明白了
No, I got it.
是的，我们在上面
Yeah, we're on top of it.
可以谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
现在，那条该死的鱼在哪里？
Now, where's that damn fish?
在那里我抓到他了
There. I've got him.
对不起，只是海豚
Sorry, it's just the dolphins.
宝贝们，请不要插手
Babies, stay out of it, please.
我已经安装了救生索
And I've rigged a lifeline.
让泵把你推出去用 把你拉回来的绳子
Just let the pumps push you out and use the rope to pull yourself back in.
正确的
Right.
为什么不 我拍所有的电影？
And why don't I do all the filming?
我要两个摄像头我们需要保险 快点，杰克！
I want both cameras. We need the coverage. Come on, Jack!
这不是野餐
This isn't a picnic.
这部电影太血腥了 退休年金
This film is a bloody retirement annuity.
如果你能 只做了一件事
I'd feel better if you did just the one thing.
怎么了？
What's the matter?
脚发冷了？
Getting cold feet?
好吧，鲍勃别动 就在那里
Okay, Bob. Hold it about right there.
我们就在隧道的正上方 好吧，我们都在这里
We're right over the tunnel. Okay, we're all set down here.
告诉菲茨罗伊斯 我们已就位
Tell FitzRoyce we 're in position.
菲茨罗伊斯，你现在可以走了
FitzRoyce, you can go now.
他们重新测试生命线 看看它是否安全
They're testing the lifeline to see if it's secure.
他们是些密友 你知道，鱼油和血
They're spreadin' some chum. You know, fish oil and blood.
然后杰克会 一些金属的声音
Then Jack's gonna make some metallic sounds.
把她吸引下来 进入过滤管
to attract her right down into that filtration pipe.
启动泵
Start the pumps.
你明白了
You got it.
- 它进来了！ - 他明白了！
- It's in! - He's got it!
好吧它已锁定
All right. It's locked.
很安全，布罗迪 去争取吧
It's safe, Brody. Go for it.
好吧，我们走吧
Okay, let's go.
这是控制 那条隧道有没有修好？
This is Control. Is that tunnel patch in place?
容易的
Easy.
我来帮你 说完了，摩根医生
Let me help you with that, Dr. Morgan.
知道了！
Got it!
现在焊接 狗娘养的
Now weld the son-of-a-bitch…
凯瑟琳，你在干什么；？
Kathryn, what are you doin'?
我要去那里
I'm going down there.
你疯了？
You crazy?
他需要眼睛在后面 他的头，卡尔文
He needs eyes in the back of his head, Calvin.
谢谢，弗雷德 好吧
Thanks, Fred. All right.
小心坦克
Watch the tanks.
可以
Okay.
这是你的鳍 谢谢
Here are your fins. Thanks.
小心下面
Be careful down there now.
你还好吧？
You all right?
菲茨罗伊斯先生在哪里？
Where's Mr. FitzRoyce?
我不知道
I have no idea.
发生了什么？
What's goin' on?
不，不！
Guv'nor!
没有其他出路了吗？
There's no other way out?
你不明白 就这样！
You don't understand. This is it!
你看了吗？
Have you looked?
他没有上来
He didn't come up.
也不是，你这个该死的混蛋 回答我！
Guv'nor, you bloody bastard. Answer me!
我们会让那婊子窒息的 关闭泵
We'll suffocate the bitch. Shut down the pumps.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
我们为什么不炸掉它？ 听着，侄子
Why don't we blow it up? Listen, nephew.
那是一台250万美元的涡轮机 因为一些该死的鱼而冒烟！
That's a $2.5 million turbine that's not going up in smoke because of some damn fish!
现在关闭泵！
Now shut the pumps down!
发生了什么事？
What's happened?
他们已经把水泵关掉了
They've shut the pumps off.
她只需要这些 大门关不上多久
That's all she needs. The gates can't hold much longer.
菲利普，拔出别针！ 拔出别针，菲利普
Philip, pull the pin! Pull the pin, Philip.
看那个！
Look at that!
天哪！
Jesus!
哦，天哪！
Oh, my God!
我们得警告他们 我们得告诉他们！
We gotta warn 'em. We gotta tell 'em!
起来！
Get 'em up!
它回来了 快起来！
It's coming back. Get 'em up quick!
快点！快点！ 快点！
Come on! Hurry up! Come on!
起来！
Get 'em up!
快点，迈克 出去！
Come on, Mike. Get out of there!
- 快点，迈克！ - 起来！
- Come on, Mike! - Get 'em up!
快点！
Come on!
开门！
Pull the door!
怎么会松了？
How the hell did it get loose?
打开舱门！
Open the hatch!
上来吧， 迈克我明白了
Come on up, Mike. I gotcha.
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
我们有压力吗 在那些隧道里？
Do we have pressure in those tunnels yet?
是的然后打开舱壁， 把那些人弄出去
Affirmative. Then open up the bulkheads, get those people out of there.
完成
Done.
感受空气！ 你能感觉到空气吗？
Feel the air! Can you feel the air?
水在往下流 水要沉了！
The water's going down. The water's going down!
尽量保持冷静 不要冲到门口
Try to be calm. Don't rush to the door.
我们重新得救了！
We're saved!
哦！我们做到了！
Oh! We did it!
其他人，迈克 其他的呢？
The others, Mike. What about the others?
卡尔文成功了丽莎
Calvin made it. Lisa.
迈克迈克！海豚！
Mike. Mike! The dolphins!
辛迪！
Cindy!
- 辛迪！ - 桑迪！
- Cindy! - Sandy!
加油，姑娘们！辛迪！ 辛迪！
Come on, girls! Cindy! Cindy!
哦，好女孩桑迪！
Oh, good girl. Sandy!
桑迪，来吧，宝贝 桑迪，你在哪儿？
Sandy, come on, baby. Sandy, where are you?
美琪桑迪！
MIKEI Sandy!
我希望她成功了
I hope she made it.
辛迪，留下来 桑迪
Cindy, stay. Sandy.
桑迪！
Sandy!
好吧！
All right!